<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Have You Played It?</title>
    <link>https://hypi.pages.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Have You Played It?</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://hypi.pages.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Altos Odysee</title>
      <link>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/altos-odysee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/altos-odysee/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Alto&amp;rsquo;s Odyssey is a simple adventure game developed by Noodlecake, a mesmerizing journey through the sand. The game is rated for 3+. The game has a download count of 10,000,000+. This game is a sequel to Alto&amp;rsquo;s Adventure, which was a huge success. About this game The game is all about Alto and his friends, who set off on an endless sandboarding journey. The game has most beautifull and simple intro screen with various background sets or seasons such as rainy, dawn, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zombie Catchers</title>
      <link>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/zombie-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/zombie-game/</guid>
      <description>About this game Zombie Catchers by Deca Games is a casual action-adventure game in a futuristic world riddled with a zombie invasion. It is a mid-violence game rated for 7+. The game has a download count of 1,000,000,000+.&#xA;According to this game, planet Earth is affected by the zombie virus, and most of the people have turned into zombies. At this time, there are two intergalactic businessmen, A.J. and Bud, who have decided to build a business empire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger of stick 5</title>
      <link>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/anger-of-stick-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hypi.pages.dev/blog/anger-of-stick-5/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A game by COWON and BUTTON E&amp;amp;M,this game is about a lone stickman(Player) in a zombie infested world fighting off enemies including zombies and people who supports them while saving innocent citizen from hands of the enemies.&#xA;Available on playstore free to download.&#xA;It is a mid violence games rated for 7+. The game has a download of 1000,000,000+ downloads.&#xA;Note to Readers The review is completely based on personal experience and the gameplay and features may change in some devices.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
